our eighth hostage so we got all the boring crap out of the way in the last
我们的第八个人 质，所以我们得到了所有 无聊的废话在最后
video so let's start learning something cool the first thing I want to show you guys is basically how to create a new
视频 让我们开始学习一些东西 很酷， 我想 告诉你 的第一件事 伙计们基本上是如何创造新的
image from cutting out an area of your original image so this of course is my
从 切出你的区域的 图像 原始图像 所以这当然是我的
original image next let me show you in Photoshop so say that we want to take
原始图片接下来让我 告诉 你 Photoshop所以说我们想要
this and I don't know maybe we need to crop it because we're using it as a
这个，我不知道也许我们 需要 裁剪它因为我们用它作为一个
profile picture on a website or something or maybe we just only wanted part of this because my ex-girlfriend
网站上的个人资料图片或 某事或者我们 只是想要的 部分原因是因为我的前女友
was on the side so we wanted to crop her out so what we can do using pillow is
在旁边所以我们想要裁剪她 所以我们可以用枕头做什么
essentially this we can crop out for example a piece of this image right here and pretty much cut it and save this
基本上我们可以裁剪出来 例如，这张图片就在这里 和 几乎削减它并妥善保存本
portion as a new image so let's go ahead and learn how to do that and let me
部分作为一个新的形象所以让我们 继续前进 并学习如何做到这一点让 我
close out of this alright so I deleted the other two lines so I kept the first one and the last one pretty much created
关闭这个好吧 所以 我删除了 另外两 行所以我保留了第一行 一个， 最后一个 创造了 很多
an object from this image and displayed it in Photoshop so the first thing that
此图像中 的 对象 并显示 它在Photoshop 这样的第一件事
we need to do is we need to give it the area that we want to crop so I'm going
我们需要 做的是，我们需要给 它 我们想要 裁剪的区域， 所以我要去
to set it equal to area and it's actually a 4 item couple the first two
设置它等于 区域，它是 实际上是一个4项，前两个
parameters are the X&Y coordinates of the top left corner so 100 100 so
参数的 X和Y坐标 左上角所以100 100所以
actually let me probably shouldn't have deleted that alright so we'll say that
实际上让我可能不应该 删除那 没关系，所以 我们会说
we want to start at 100 over and 100 down so this is going to be our starting
我们 想从100开始和100开始 所以这将 是我们的开始
point and we'll say that we'll crop to like I don't know like 300 and 375 so in
点 ，我们会说，我们将农作物 就像我不知道 像 300 和 375这样
order to do that the other parameters are 300 and 375 now another thing I want to point out is whenever you're making
为了做其他参数 300和375 现在是我想要的另一件事 要指出的是你什么时候制作
your tupple right here make sure that you don't go outside the main image area
你的tupple就在这里确保 你不要走出主图像区域
so for example you can't start at 100 100 and end up at like I don't know 600
所以例如你不能从100开始 100 ，最后就像我不知道600
700 because that's off your original image so
700，因为那是你原来的 形象如此
just watch out for that so this is the area that we want to crop so now what we
只是注意 这一点，所以这是的 我们想要 裁剪的 区域 现在我们
have to basically say is create a new image from this cropped image well the
不得不基本上说是创造一个 新的 来自这个 裁剪图像的图像很好
first thing we need is to be able to store this new image in its own object so I'm going to name my new image
我们需要的第一件事就是 能够 将此新图像存储在自己的对象中 所以我要命名我的新形象
cropped image and now in order to crop it take your original image and call the
裁剪图像，现在为了 裁剪 它会拍摄原始 图像并调用
function crop now this crop function the only parameter that it takes is a four
功能裁剪现在这个作物功能 了 只需要四个参数
digit tupple with the parameters or the coordinates of where to crop oh that's
数字 tupple与参数或 裁剪的地方坐标哦
convenient we have one right there so I'm going to take this and pass it in
方便我们有一个权利 我要接受这个并传递它
and you can actually throw this entire thing right in here without the need for the area variable but then you have
而你实际上可以抛出 这整个 没有 必要的东西就在这里 区域变量，但你有
these double parenthesis and it gets kind of messy so this is actually the
这些双括号， 它得到 有点乱， 所以这实际上是
best way to do it so what we're basically saying is take this original
这样做的最佳方式 就是我们 所做的 基本上说是拿这个原件
image of Bucky and crop out an area with these coordinates and store that new image in this cropped image so now if we
Bucky的 形象， 并用一个区域裁剪出来 这些 坐标 和存储新的 此裁剪图像中的图像现在 如果我们
actually just show this what it's going to do whenever you run this is check
实际上只是展示了它的发展方向 每次运行时都要检查
this out now the reason that we have two of these is because this is the one I
现在这就是 我们有两个 原因 这些是因为 这是我
was demonstrating this is the one that opened with this line right here and
证明了这就是那个 这条线开通就在这里 和
whenever I ran this line look at what it did pretty stinking cool so this is our
每当我跑这条线时，看看它是什么 确实很臭，所以这是我们的
original image and this is our new cropped image and later on I'm going to
原始图像，这 是我们的新 裁剪图像，然后我要去
be showing you guys how to you know whatever you want to do with it whether
展示 你们 怎么知道 无论你想做什么， 是否
you want to upload it to the internet or just save it as a JPEG or ping whatever
你想要把 它上传 到互联网或 只需将 其 保存 为 JPEG或ping任何东西
but that is how you do that
但那 就是 你这样做的方式